<Page xmlns="http://schemas.nativescript.org/tns.xsd" navigatingTo="onNavigatingTo">
    
    <GridLayout rows="auto" columns="auto" width="100" height="100" class="menu">
    <StackLayout row="0" col="0" class="line"></StackLayout>
    <StackLayout row="0" col="0" class="line"></StackLayout>
    <StackLayout row="0" col="0" class="line"></StackLayout>
</GridLayout>

    <ActionBar title="About Me" icon="" />
<ScrollView>
    <StackLayout class="p-2">
     <Image src="~/Images/YO.jpg"
        width="40%"
        aspect="aspectFill"/>
        <StackLayout height="50"></StackLayout>
        
    <Label class="text-base leading-tight" textWrap="true" text="¡Hola! I'm an international student hailing from the vibrant country of Mexico, and I've been on an exciting journey in the United States for the past four years. 
    Currently, I'm on the verge of completing my degree in Computer Science, having previously earned an associate's degree in Computer Information Technology. 
    Technology is my passion; it's not just a career choice, but a genuine love affair. My diverse professional experience spans from roles as a secretary and manager to donning the apron as a Starbucks barista. In the realm of IT, I've thrived as a Technician Support Specialist, relishing every opportunity to troubleshoot and find innovative solutions. 
    When I'm not immersed in the digital world, you'll often find me in pursuit of the perfect cup of coffee. The art of brewing and the nuances of flavor profiles truly fascinate me. I'm a staunch advocate for the power of marketing, recognizing its influence in shaping our connected world.
    Recently, I've discovered a newfound love for badminton and dedicated hours at the gym to stay active and healthy. It's become a gratifying part of my routine, offering both physical and mental rejuvenation.
    Beyond my personal interests, I'm deeply passionate about advocating for the safety and wellbeing of vulnerable children. Their protection is a cause that resonates deeply with me, particularly for those facing situations of abuse, abandonment, or sexual assault. I believe every child deserves a safe and nurturing environment, and I'm committed to playing my part in ensuring this reality.
    I'm honored to have been recognized as the Outstanding Graduate Student in Computer Information Technology at my college. This achievement speaks to my dedication and commitment to excelling in my field, and I'm eager to continue pushing boundaries and contributing to the ever-evolving tech landscape." />

        <StackLayout height="20"></StackLayout>  <!-- This creates a space of 20 dip (device-independent pixels)
        <Button text="Home" onTap="goToHome" ></Button>  -->
    </StackLayout>
     </ScrollView>
</Page>
